http://www.flowserve.com/privacy

LOG IN
Forgot Password?
New User? Register here.
Cookie Settings
Flowserve is a leading provider of flow control products and services for the global infrastructure markets. Flowserve recognizes and supports the privacy interests of all persons, and we respect these interests when we collect and process Personal Data. This Privacy Notice explains our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Data is collected and used through our websites.
Flowserve and its affiliates (collectively “Flowserve”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) maintain and operate this and other websites including applications (collectively, the “Flowserve Websites” or “Websites”). Because some applications, such as those hosted by a third party on our behalf, may require additional information, or use information in a different way, they may have their own privacy policies and terms and conditions. These applications may also offer you additional choices for managing your Personal Data.
APPLICABILITY OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE
This Privacy Notice applies to all visitors and users of the Flowserve Websites. Because Flowserve is a multinational corporation, we may adopt separate privacy policies or additional provisions as necessary to reflect the requirements of applicable local laws in the countries in which we operate.
INFORMATION FLOWSERVE COLLECTS
Personal Data
You may browse many sections of our Websites without providing Personal Data about yourself. However, if you choose to establish a business relationship, apply for employment with us or use the “Contact Us” function, we will collect certain information. Flowserve collects the following categories of information about you:
If we establish a business relationship with you, we collect relevant business information, such as name, contact details including email, account, transaction information and/or any other information provided by you relevant to the business relationship.
If you seek employment with us through the Websites, we collect your name, contact details, the position(s) you’re applying for, your education, employment history and any other information you choose to provide in connection with your application for employment.
If you choose to fill out the “Contact Us” form, we collect contact information that may include your name, email address, phone number, as well as your comments and correspondence in connection with the request.
If you browse through our website, we will collect information regarding your device, actions and preferences such as login, font and other display preferences to deliver a better and more personalized service, some of which may be considered Personal Data.
Collectively, the above categories of information constitute “Personal Data”. Missing or incomplete information may result in Flowserve being unable to perform, or continue to perform, a transaction with you or on your behalf.
USE OF INFORMATION
We use your information to improve your experience and to facilitate the business relationship. Situations where we may use your information, include:
To conduct our business, including fulfilling your requests for products, services, and support, and to create new business.
To communicate about our products and services for marketing purposes.
To carry out the obligations arising from any agreements entered between you and us.
To maintain and improve our Websites, enhance your user experience, tailor the user experience, and to ensure content on the Websites are relevant.
To protect the security of the Websites, our systems, and you.
To comply with our legal obligations.
DATA PROTECTION AND SECURITY MEASURES
Maintaining the security of your information is very important to Flowserve. We use reasonable technologies to keep your Personal Data secure, and we implement reasonable security measures, that are designed to protect against the accidental or unlawful destruction loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to your Personal Data.
PROCESSING OF INFORMATION
Flowserve is a multinational corporation, headquartered in the United States with offices, affiliates, employees, representatives, partners, and service providers located around the world. As a result, Flowserve may transfer your information, including your Personal Data to, or process your information in, the United States and/or countries other than the country in which your information was collected or provided.
RECIPIENTS OF INFORMATION
We may share your information, including your Personal Data within the Flowserve group of affiliates to facilitate the business relationship and provide the best customer experience. Furthermore, we may share your information with third parties that assist us with fulfillment of our business objectives, job applicant screening or with the performance and content of our Websites. In the event we sell, assign or transfer all or part of the Flowserve business, we may transfer your personal data to the buyer.
CHOICES REGARDING COMMUNICATIONS
If you no longer wish to receive any marketing communications, remain on a mailing list to which you previously subscribed, or receive any other communication from Flowserve, please follow the unsubscribe link in the applicable communication.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Website who are California residents to request a notice identifying the categories of Personal Data we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please submit a written request, specifying that you would like a “California Privacy Notice,” to the following address:
Flowserve Corporation
5215 North O'Connor Boulevard, Suite 2300
Irving, Texas 75039 USA
Attn: Legal Department
COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser when you visit a website. Flowserve Websites use cookies and other tracking technology information to enhance your user experience, analyze site usage, and assist in our marketing efforts. Information collected may be shared with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.
We classify cookies in the following categories:
Strictly Necessary
Performance
Functional
Targeting
Because we respect your right to privacy, you can choose not to allow some types of cookies. You may accept or reject each cookie category, except strictly necessary, by changing your "cookie settings". However, if you reject cookies, you may impact your experience on our Website and the services we are able to offer. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
While Flowserve does not sell personal data in exchange for any monetary consideration, we do share personal data for business purposes that could be deemed a “sale,” as defined by the CCPA (Cal.Civ.Code 1798.140(t)(1)). This includes sharing identifiers or other electronic network activity with website analytical companies and third parties with embedded content in our Website. The following third parties have embedded content on our Website and may attach targeting cookies:
Google Analytics
YouTube and Google Ad Services
DoubleClick
LinkedIn
Pardot
HubSpot
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Flowserve Websites may provide links or other directions to the websites of our distributors, sales representatives or other third parties. If you follow a link to a third-party website, please note that we are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any Personal Data you provide while visiting such websites. We encourage you to read third-party websites’ privacy policies and statements.
DO NOT TRACK
Flowserve does not track users’ behavior on our Websites or across websites for the purpose of serving targeted ads, and therefore our Websites do not respond to browser Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Third parties that have content embedded on Flowserve’s Websites may set cookies on a user’s browser and/or obtain information about the fact that a web browser visited a specific Flowserve Website from a certain IP address. Third parties cannot collect any other Personal Data from Flowserve’s websites unless you provide it to them.
PRIVACY OF CHILDREN
Flowserve’s Websites are general audience Websites. We do not intentionally collect Personal Data from users of the Websites who are under the age of sixteen (16). We request that such individuals do not provide Personal Data.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE
Flowserve may update this Privacy Notice from time to time as our business, services, or policies change, or as required by law. We encourage you to visit our Websites periodically to stay informed about Flowserve's privacy practices. If we update this Privacy Notice, we will post the updated version of the Privacy Notice on our Websites. Your use of the website following any update to the Notice means that you accept the updated Privacy Notice.
CONTACT US
Flowserve takes reasonable steps to ensure your Personal Data is accurate and up-to-date for the purposes for which it was collected. We encourage you to contact us to update or correct your information if it changes or if you believe that any information we collected about you is inaccurate. Please note that to honor your request, we may require additional information for authentication or other verification purposes.
For any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or our processing of your Personal Data, please contact Flowserve at privacy@flowserve.com and our Data Privacy team at Flowserve Corporation, 5215 North O'Connor Boulevard, Suite 2300, Irving, Texas 75039 USA.
ADDITIONAL TERMS FOR EU OR EEA VISITORS and USERS
This section of our Privacy Notice (“Additional Terms for EU Visitors and Users”) explains Flowserve’s commitment to comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Flowserve is committed to fulfilling our responsibilities in relation to collection, retention, use and other processing of Personal Data that is within the scope of GDPR. Such Personal Datawill be processed only for lawful and appropriate purposes. Flowserve has implemented reasonable measures designed to secure Personal Data and to prevent unauthorized or accidental access, erasure, or other misuse of personal data. Flowserve will facilitate the exercise of Data Subject rights in an effective and transparent manner.
APPLICATION OF ADDITIONAL TERMS
The Additional Terms for EU and EEA Visitors and Users applies when:
The Data Subject creates or shares Personal Data via a relationship with Flowserve and is located within the European Union (EU) or the European Economic Area (EEA);
Such relationship is within the scope of GDPR; and
Flowserve functions as a Data Controller when processing the Personal Data for such Data Subject.
Should the above Privacy Notice or other Privacy Notices at Flowserve conflict with the Additional Terms for EU or EEA Visitors and Users, this section will prevail as to Data Subjects in the EU or EEA.
HOW WE CONDUCT CROSS-BORDER TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Flowserve may transfer your Personal Data across borders to Flowserve and our representatives, affiliates, third party partners and service providers in the United States and other countries where we do business. In the event of a cross-border transfer of your Personal Data, if the country to which we transfer your Personal Data is not a recipient of an adequacy decision from the European Commission, and if the transfer is not made under a derogation that does not require additional suitable protections, then we provide appropriate or suitable safeguards for such cross-border transfers as required by law, via the EU standard contractual clauses.
AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING
Flowserve does not use automated decision-making, including profiling, in a way that produces legal effects concerning you or that similarly significantly affects you. We also do not use automated decision-making, including profiling, based on any special categories of Personal Data.
RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA
Flowserve retains your Personal Data only for as long as is reasonably necessary to accomplish the purposes for which it was collected, and as permitted by applicable law. In many cases, this will require retention through the period of the business relationship, or as needed for business administration, tax and/or legal purposes. We may retain backups and archives that may include your Personal Data as long as reasonably necessary to comply with applicable law.
SPECIAL CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA
Flowserve will not, other than in exceptional circumstances, collect and process any special categories of your Personal Data.
YOUR RIGHTS
GDPR grants rights to Data Subjects regarding the processing of Personal Data. With regards to your Personal Data, you may have the right to:
Request access to your Personal Data;
Request rectification of your Personal Data;
Request erasure of your Personal Data (e.g., update or correct your Personal Data);
Request to restrict our processing of your Personal Data;
Object to our processing of your Personal Data;
Request data portability;
Withdraw consent to the processing of your Personal Data (without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before withdrawal); and/or
Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
In certain circumstances, Flowserve will need to use your Personal Data even though you may have asked us to delete or restrict or if you objected to our use of it. If this is necessary, we will do so in a lawful, fair and transparent manner. Furthermore, if you revoke consent, prior uses and disclosures will not be affected, and we may otherwise continue to process Personal Data as permitted or required by law.
CONTACT US
To exercise your rights or for any questions regarding this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or our processing of your Personal Data, please contact Flowserve at privacy@flowserve.com and its Data Privacy team at Flowserve Corporation, 5215 North O'Connor Boulevard, Suite 2300, Irving, Texas 75039 USA.
Updated October 1, 2020
SHARE
Investor Relations
Terms and Conditions
Privacy
Anti-Slavery/Human Trafficking Statement
Library
Contact Us
